http://ellia.org/privacy-policy/

Annual Report by the Chairwoman
Statuts of the “Association Angevine de la Bibliothèque Anglophone”
Privacy Policy
Dear members,
Here at the English-language Library in Angers your privacy is important to us. If you have signed up to receive our newsletter “Postcard from the Library,” we would like to inform you of our privacy policy in accordance with the European Union’s (EU) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
The GDPR mandates a new level of protection for the collection, storage and use of personal data. This allows you to have more control over what happens to your information. For example, you have the right to unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time and your email will be subsequently deleted from the mailing list. You may also request the removal of your personal information by contacting us directly. You have the right to be informed about how your information is used. Here at the library, your email is used, with your consent, to keep you posted on upcoming events and activities. The data we collect must be disassociated from personal information such as your name. This is why when you sign-up for the newsletter we only collect your email. We share your email with a third-party company, Mailjet, an automated newsletter provider which is also in compliance with the GDPR policies. If you would like more details on Mailjet’s GDPR compliance click here.
If you have any specific concerns regarding GDPR compliance or your privacy, please direct your questions to info@ellia.org.
Upcoming EventsCoffee House: CANCELLED 11/12/2020Knit and Natter: CANCELLED 11/12/2020Reading Shakespeare by ZOOM 11/12/2020Saturday Reading Group by ZOOM 12/12/2020Join in for the library's traditional Christmas caroling...time to lift our spirits in song! 13/12/2020Pizza and Board Games: CANCELLED 15/12/2020Take your TOEIC test 16/12/2020Books and Tea by ZOOM 17/12/2020Coffee House: CANCELLED 18/12/2020Knit and Natter: CANCELLED 18/12/2020Saturday Reading Group 16/01/2021Pizza and Board Games 19/01/2021Book Club reads "The Only Story" 22/01/2021Garden Club Meeting - Seed Exchange & Garden Visits Program for 2021 04/02/2021Saturday Reading Group 13/02/2021Calendar
<<
Dec 2020
>>
MTWTFSS
30
1
2
3
Follow us!
Load More…Follow on Instagram
